qvalent.com 2007-01-25

# Qvalent: Procurement, Presentment and Payment

This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire Web site. 

Qvalent values your privacy and recognises the sensitivity of your personal information. The personal information you provide will be treated carefully and appropriately as outlined in our Privacy Policy. You can visit the Qvalent™ Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name, company, phone contacts and e-mail address. The following statement outlines the specifics related to our use of personal information. 

Collection and Use of Information  
When you signup for Qvalent's email newsletter or complete any request forms on the Qvalent web site, some personal information is required. By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Policy. This information is used for the following purposes. 

To service your request for information or services offered by Qvalent. To help us create Web site content most relevant and useful to you. To alert you to key announcements, new service offerings and updated information from Qvalent. Signup Information Signup information includes information collected during initial registration or application for Qvalent offerings, as well as any additional information provided to gain access to special services or features. These special services may include software downloads, application submission, program participation, email newsletters and more. 

This information is used by Qvalent solely to inform you of new services and programs and to improve the value of this web site. Qvalent does not, sell, trade, rent, or otherwise transfer your personal information to third parties. We may, however, release personally identifying information when necessary to comply with state and federal laws. In such a case, we will do our best to notify you of any such release by contacting you through e-mail or by letter, if we are able to. 

Web Site Traffic and Analysis  
Qvalent gathers and analyses information from our visitors' routine use of the web site. We use this information to monitor what areas of the site are most active, and to help focus our continuing development efforts. 

Opting Out  
If at any time you wish to not receive any notices or additional information from Qvalent, simply notify us via e-mail and we will promptly remove you from our distribution. 

Qvalent requires users to provide the information in the registration screens for reasons specified and to properly service your request. As greater functionality is added to the site, we will continue to strive to develop mechanisms and policies that best address participants' preferences related to information collection and use. 

Links to Third Party Sites and Services (if applicable)  
Qvalent may provide you with links to the websites of third parties. In the event you choose to access such websites, Qvalent is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. We recommend that you check the applicable privacy policy of such party before providing personally identifiable information to it, as its privacy policy may differ from Qvalent. 

Additionally, we may periodically conduct user and customer surveys. In all cases, your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if a third party conducts the survey. While we choose our survey providers carefully, it should be noted that the privacy policy for any third party collection services might differ from Qvalent. Wherever possible, links to that party's privacy policy are provided and should be consulted. Qvalent is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties. 

Security  
Qvalent takes every reasonable precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website (such as name, address, phone number and e-mail), that information is secured behind our internal firewall to which we restrict all outside access. Despite the use of secure technology to protect your information, you should be aware that no security system is foolproof. While Qvalent attempts to prevent unauthorised persons from accessing our files or tampering with our website, we cannot guarantee that these efforts will be successful. Qvalent is not liable for disclosures of user information due to errors in transmission or unauthorised acts of third parties. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

Cookies  
Like most web sites, the Qvalent.com site uses "cookies" to allow you to move more quickly through the our web site. Cookies are small text files a web site can use to recognise repeat users and facilitate their ongoing access to and use of the site. Cookies do not collect personally identifying information, but collect information related to the characteristics of your computer, or when and how you reached the Qvalent.com site. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Qvalent cannot control the use of cookies by advertisers or third parties hosting data for Qvalent. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature. Please note that cookies may be necessary to enable you to use certain features on the Qvalent.com site. 

Children's Privacy  
Please note that our website does not market to children. We do not want to collect any personal information from minors under any circumstances. We ask that minors (under age 18) refrain from using our site. Anyone using this Site or the Services warrants and promises that they are 18 years of age or older. 

Changes in our Privacy Policy  
Qvalent recognises the need to update this privacy policy as new features and services are offered on Qvalent.com. Qvalent reserves the right to amend the privacy policy at any time with or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes to our Privacy Policy. 

Last Update: October, 2001 

How to Contact Us  
We invite your questions or comments about our privacy practices, and your experience with our site and services. Please contact us at [info@qvalent.com](mailto:info@qvalent.com). 

Legal notification  
Unless otherwise explicitly stated herein, any non-personal information or material sent to Qvalent will be deemed NOT to be confidential. By sending Qvalent any non-personal information or material, you grant Qvalent an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute those materials or information, and you also agree that Qvalent is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purpose. However, we will not release your name or otherwise publicise the fact that you submitted materials or other information to us unless: (a) you grant us permission to do so; (b) we first notify you that the materials or other information you submit to a particular part of a site will be published or otherwise used with your name on it; or (c) we are required to do so by law.
